NYSUT Mid-Hudson Regional Office Files. 6174/011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- WFW-Attendance and Leave Policy, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  Draft Wappingers district staff attendance and leave policy, with cover letter to unit presidents from assistant superintendent
- WFW-Custodians and Others-Classified Work Duties, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  7/1/93. Grievance re classification work duties for custodians, performed by others after an event, depriving unit members opportunity for overtime
- WFW-Agreements and Constitution, 1985-1990 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  Constitution of Wappingers Federation of Educational Assistants; Improper Practice charge by WFEA against district for failure to deduct dues; collective bargaining agreement between district and Wappingers Federation of Educational Assistants
- WFW Grievances (folder 1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Tracking sheets for Wappingers Congress of Teachers/Wappingers Federation of Workers grievances 357-399, including descriptions
- WFW Grievances (folder 2 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Tracking sheets for Wappingers Congress of Teachers/Wappingers Federation of Workers grievances 400-439, including descriptions
- WFW Grievances (folder 3 of 4), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Tracking sheets for Wappingers Congress of Teachers/Wappingers Federation of Workers grievances 266-329, including descriptions
- WFW Grievances (folder 4 of 4), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Tracking sheets for Wappingers Congress of Teachers/Wappingers Federation of Workers grievances 194-444, including descriptions and summary list